cashle.com 2016-04-05

# Points2shop - Earn Points for Free Rewards

**Last updated:** 5/20/2014

**1\. Overview**

This document establishes the privacy policies of Points2Shop LLC, its websites and mobile applications, as well as its compliance with specific national and international jurisdictions (including the privacy regulations and laws thereof). The publication of this document rescinds all previous privacy policies – implied, spoken or written – and establishes

**2\. Organization Information**

The principal activities of Points2Shop LLC are affiliate marketing and advertising.  
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of Points2Shop LLC.  
Points2Shop LLC is based in United States and at the following postal address:  
3625 Brookside Parkway, Suite 300  
Alpharetta, GA, 30022  
United States of America  
Points2Shop LLC can be reached via e-mail at [info@points2shop.com](mailto:info@points2shop.com)

**3\. Anonymous Access**

Visitors can access the website/application home pages and browse sites/applications without disclosing personal data.

**4\. Services and Links**

Points2Shop LLC websites and mobile applications allow communication with other visitors and post information that can be accessed by other visitors. Communication via these posts is voluntary. All information communicated is the responsibility and discretion of the individual and may be collected by other visitors. Points2Shop LLC sites and applications may include links to third-party web/mobile service providers. Points2Shop LLC is not responsible for the content, accuracy, or privacy policies of third-party web/mobile services.

**5\. Automatic Data Collection**

Points2shop may collect information from your computer, mobile phone or other access device. The information sent to us includes, but is not limited to, data on the pages you access, your computer IP address, referral data, device identifiers, the type of operating system you’re using, your location (GPS), mobile network information, standard web log data and other information. Web log data includes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from our site to determine trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**6\. Data Collection and Purpose**

We may use the personal data supplied or provided by you to send you emails and/or push (mobile) notifications containing invitations for participation in promotions, including, but not limited to, offers and market research survey opportunities offered by our clients and/or partners. Your participation in these opportunities is completely voluntary and you can opt-out at any time of promotional emails because Points2Shop employs a strict email policy against sending unsolicited emails. You may opt out by changing your email settings in the Edit Account/Edit Preferences section. Please note that opting out from promotional emails does not exempt you from receiving administrative emails about your account status and membership status changes, Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions updates.

Additionally, we may share personal data and demographic information we collect from you with our clients or partners in connection with promotions like offers and market research surveys opportunities, offered by our clients or partners for several purposes, including, without limitation, facilitating your participation in a survey(s), offers, fraud detection and prevention, copyright infringement, data validation, incentive or reward fulfillment (if applicable), identifying respondents for re-contact surveys and offers, or communications, database matching, data append, coding, data segmentation, and/or developing data insights regarding survey and offer participants, but not for marketing purposes.

Access to collected personal data is available upon request. You can review your personal information at any time by logging in to your account and browsing to http://www.points2shop.com/account/index.

We reserve the right to share your identity with others within the stipulations of data protection in an attempt to prevent further fraudulent activity. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as identity verification services

**7\. Sharing and Cookies**

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this occurrence. Not accepting cookies may make certain features of Points2shop.com unavailable to you; though we will make every effort to ensure that users who have disabled cookies are denied access only to those portions of the website that legitimately require cookies for their functionality. To opt-out of these cookies and for more information, please visit aboutads.info/choices and/or networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

Points2shop assists clients and/or partners in recruiting for their online/mobile ad exposure programs. In connection with a client’s and/or partner’s online/mobile ad exposure program, you can participate in offers and market research surveys regarding specific online ads and promotions that our client or partner is testing for its client. To facilitate the completion of these offers and surveys, we and/or our client/partner may write, set or read first and third party cookies, locally shared/stored objects, flash cookies, and/or any other related technology (each a “Cookie Technology” and collectively the “Cookie Technologies”). The Cookie Technologies may be written, set or read in various locations, including and without limitation, on our and/or our client/partner’s website(s), system(s), or server(s). If you participate, a unique identification number and a source identification number may be stored in the Cookie Technology, to allow you to be re-contacted about the online ad or promotion and to determine whether you have seen, clicked on or otherwise interacted with the online ad or promotion. If you have interacted with the online ad or promotion, our client or partner will send us your unique identification number and a link to the specific survey or offer on the online ad or promotion and you will receive an email invitation to participate in and complete the survey once opt-in for email. Survey participation is completely voluntary and you can opt-out at any time. If you do not wish to participate in the Online Ad Exposure Program, please visit http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs&nav=1 and http://www.safecount.net/viewyourcookiesinformation_optinout.php.

Points2shop may allow other companies, called third party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on Points2shop.com or within our mobile applications. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows them to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you or others, who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Points2shop does not have access to or control over the cookies that may be placed by these parties on your computer, and has no control over these parties' privacy policies or information collection practices.

**8\. Children's Privacy**

Points2Shop LLC does not knowingly collect personal data from individuals under the age of 13. Minors 13 to 18 are permitted to access the services of the site only with parental permission. It is the responsibility of the individual and the parent to ensure such permissions are obtained. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this and as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers.

**9\. Disclosure**

Except as set forth herein, Points2Shop LLC does not disclose personal data to subsidiaries or other organizations without your permission or where it can reasonably be inferred from the circumstances that you consent to the disclosure to the third parties. Points2shop tries to limit the information it provides to third parties to the information they need to help Points2shop provide goods and services to you.

**10\. Third Party Advertisements**

The Points2shop websites, mobile applications and emails contain links to various other sites that are not owned by us. While Points2shop makes every effort to ensure that our advertisers post clear and complete Privacy Policies and observe appropriate data practices, each of these sites/applications has a privacy policy that may differ from that of Points2shop. The privacy practices of other websites/applications and companies are not covered by this policy. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites/applications. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site/application and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collect personally identifiable information.

Points2shop may share non-personally identifiable information collected via the service in aggregate, anonymous form with advertisers or other third parties so that they may better evaluate what products and services are most appealing to different segments of the user base. Points2shop does not disclose your first name/last name, address, email address or any other Personal Information to these third parties unless you give your express consent.

**11\. Confidentiality and Security**

Points2Shop LLC does not employ the use of secure transmission methods to send personal data.

Points2Shop LLC has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

Points2Shop LLC employees and data processors with access or association to the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of visitor personal data.

Points2Shop LLC does not disclose personal data to State institutions and authorities unless required by law.

**12\. Access to Personal Data**

Visitors may request access to their own specific personal information collected by Points2Shop LLC by visiting the member account information section of the Points2Shop.com website: http://www.points2shop.com/account/index.

Access to personal information may require proof of identity. Access to personal data is provided without charge. Personal data may be challenged or updated and, where appropriate, data will be completed, erased, rectified or amended. Points2Shop LLC reserves the right to refuse access to personal data. In such a case, reasons will be given for refusal.

You can close your account through our website. If you close your account, we will mark your account in our database as "Closed," but will keep your account information in our database. This is necessary to deter fraud or abuse of the site, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud or abuse of the site will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if you close your account, your personally-identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold to or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement or as required by law.

**13\. Privacy Compliance**

The Points2Shop LLC privacy policy is compliant with the following international and national regulations:

Global: OECD Privacy Guidelines on the Protection of Privacy and Transborder Flows of Personal Data Guidelines

Global: United Nations Guidelines for the Regulation of Personal Data Files Adopted by General Assembly Resolution 45/95 of 14 December 1990

United States: Privacy Act of 1974

European Union: European Convention on Human Rights

Canada: Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act

Privacy compliance is ensured by periodic self-assessment.

**14\. Privacy Support**

Enquiries or concerns about the Points2Shop LLC privacy policy can be directed to:  
Mathijs de Jong  
CEO, Points2Shop LLC  
3625 Brookside Parkway, STE 300  
Alpharetta, GA, 30022

United States of America

E-mail: [info@Points2Shop.com](mailto:info@Points2Shop.com)
